Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
The Immortal Hall follows the laws of nature.
القاعة الخالدة تتبع قوانين الطبيعة.
All the laws of nature gather as one.
تتجمع كل قوانين الطبيعة في واحد.
You're awake.
أنت مستيقظ.
You.
أنت.
Why did you bring me here?
لماذا احضرتني هنا؟
Darn it.
لعنة عليك.
Wait, wait, wait.
انتظر، انتظر، انتظر.
Don't cry, please.
لا تبكي من فضلك.
I'm trying to help you.
انا أحاول مساعدتك.
Why are you crying now?
لماذا تبكي الآن؟
Thank you for rescuing me.
شكرا لك على انقاذي.
But we've angered the Immortal Huang Xian.
لكننا أغضبنا الخالد هوانغ شيان.
If something happens in the village...
إذا حدث شيء في القرية...
my family will be in even more trouble.
عائلتي سوف تكون في ورطة أكبر.
What will my parents do?
ماذا سيفعل والدي؟
Miss.
يفتقد.
Give it back to me.
أعدها لي.
Can I ask you something?
هل يمكننى ان اسألك شيئا؟
Your village—
قريتك—
why are you all so afraid of the Immortal Huang Xian?
لماذا أنتم خائفون جدًا من الخالد هوانغ شيان؟
We're not afraid.
نحن لسنا خائفين.
We respect and revere it.
نحن نحترمه و نوقره.
They say, years ago,
يقولون منذ سنوات،
our village
قريتنا
was saved by the Immortal Huang Xian.
تم إنقاذه من قبل الخالد هوانغ شيان.
There was a plague in the village.
كان هناك وباء في القرية.
The village doctor searched everywhere for medicine, but failed.
بحث طبيب القرية في كل مكان عن الدواء، لكنه فشل.
Until one night,
حتى ليلة واحدة،
he got lost in the wild graveyard.
لقد ضاع في المقبرة البرية.
Where am I?
أين أنا؟
This isn't how it looked before.
لم يكن الأمر هكذا من قبل.
Great Immortal...
الخالد العظيم...
Spare me.
انقذني.
Great Immortal, please spare me.
أيها الخالد العظيم، أرجوك أن تنقذني.
Do I look like a human to you?
هل أبدو لك كإنسان؟
Great Immortal...
الخالد العظيم...
Please, spare me. Spare me.
من فضلك، انقذني. انقذني.
Do I look like a human to you?
هل أبدو لك كإنسان؟
Yes, yes.
نعم نعم.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
This herb
هذه العشبة
is my way of repaying your help.
هذه طريقتي في رد الجميل لمساعدتك.
Take it home and boil it in water.
خذه إلى المنزل وقم بغليه في الماء.
Thank you, Great Immortal.
شكرا لك أيها الخالد العظيم.
The doctor took the herb back and made a brew.
أخذ الطبيب العشبة مرة أخرى وصنع منها مشروبًا.
Unexpectedly,
بشكل غير متوقع،
everyone in the village
الجميع في القرية
actually recovered.
تم تعافيه فعليا.
So,
لذا،
we built the Yellow Immortal Temple.
لقد بنينا معبد الخالد الأصفر.
We've worshipped it ever since.
لقد عبدناها منذ ذلك الحين.
The Immortal Huang Xian blessed us.
باركنا الخالد هوانغ شيان.
So every new bride
لذلك كل عروس جديدة
must spend a night at the Yellow Immortal Temple.
يجب أن تقضي ليلة في معبد الخالد الأصفر.
To pray for children,
للصلاة من أجل الأطفال،
and for good fortune.
وللحظ السعيد.
There's news.
هناك اخبار.
Yes.
نعم.
The age and the artifact match.
العمر والقطعة الأثرية متطابقان.
Where is he?
أين هو؟
Zhang Family Village.
قرية عائلة تشانغ.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Get ready, we're leaving soon.
استعدوا، نحن سنغادر قريبًا.
Miss.
يفتقد.
If he really is Young Master Laifu,
إذا كان هو حقا السيد الشاب لايفو،
what will you do?
ماذا ستفعل؟
Kill him.
اقتله
The Immortal Huang Xian is angry.
الخالد هوانغ شيان غاضب.
It's because we didn't send the new bride.
لأننا لم نرسل العروس الجديدة.
Immortal Huang Xian, please calm your anger.
الخالد هوانغ شيان، من فضلك هدئ من غضبك.
I heard the Immortal Huang Xian is causing trouble here.
سمعت أن الخالد هوانغ شيان يسبب المشاكل هنا.
Who is this? I don't know him.
من هذا؟ لا أعرفه.
This Second Master Huang is a weasel who became immortal.
هذا المعلم الثاني هوانغ هو ابن عرس الذي أصبح خالدا.
If angered, he just causes mischief.
إذا غضب، فهو يسبب الأذى فقط.
Makes people act strangely.
يجعل الناس يتصرفون بغرابة.
When did he start killing people?
متى بدأ بقتل الناس؟
Who is this lady?
من هذه السيدة؟
She's from the House of Bai.
إنها من بيت باي.
From the House of Bai.
من بيت باي.
The eldest daughter of the House of Bai.
الابنة الكبرى لبيت باي.
So it's Miss Bai.
إذن فهي الآنسة باي.
Sorry for not greeting you sooner.
عذرا لعدم تحيتك في وقت سابق.
May I ask what brings you to our village?
هل يمكنني أن أسألك ما الذي أتى بك إلى قريتنا؟
You're the village chief, right?
أنت رئيس القرية، أليس كذلك؟
Yes, I am.
نعم أنا.
I'm looking for someone named Laifu.
أبحث عن شخص اسمه لايفو.
Have you seen him?
هل رأيته؟
Laifu?
جريمة؟
Chief.
رئيس.
Something happened at my house.
لقد حدث شيء في منزلي.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
Last night, I was sleeping soundly.
لقد كنت نائما بعمق الليلة الماضية.
Suddenly, I heard a rooster crow.
فجأة سمعت صوت الديك.
So I got up to take a look.
لذلك استيقظت لإلقاء نظرة.
Mom.
أم.
What are you doing up so late?
ماذا تفعلين في هذا الوقت المتأخر؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Mom.
أم.
The Immortal Huang Xian has cursed us.
لقد لعننا الخالد هوانغ شيان.
No one can escape.
لا أحد يستطيع الهروب.
It must be the Immortal Huang Xian's curse.
لا بد أن تكون لعنة الخالد هوانغ شيان.
It possessed my mother.
لقد امتلكت والدتي.
Chief.
رئيس.
It must be that boy who took Wanting.
لا بد أن يكون هذا الصبي الذي أخذ Wanting.
The Immortal Huang Xian is angry.
الخالد هوانغ شيان غاضب.
Where is he, anyway?
أين هو على أية حال؟
Who knows?
من يعلم؟
There are so many people.
هناك الكثير من الناس.
They're waiting for me.
إنهم ينتظرونني.
You're finally back.
لقد عدت أخيرا.
That's him.
هذا هو.
He's the one who took Wanting.
هو الذي أخذ Wanting.
Seems a lot happened yesterday.
يبدو أن الكثير حدث بالأمس.
So it was you causing trouble.
إذن أنت من تسبب في المشاكل.
Pretending to be the Immortal Huang Xian to stir up trouble.
يتظاهر بأنه الخالد هوانغ شيان لإثارة المشاكل.
Did you do anything to Wanting?
هل فعلت أي شيء لـWinting؟
Tie him up and offer him to the Immortal Huang Xian.
قم بربطه وتقديمه إلى الخالد هوانغ شيان.
No!
لا!
Grab him!
امسكه!
Don't run!
لا تركض!
I'm really trying to help you!
أنا أحاول حقا مساعدتك!
I didn't take her!
لم آخذها!
Tie him up!
ربطوه!
It's all your fault.
إنه خطؤك كله.
Save him?
انقذه؟
It's all because of you—him!
كل هذا بفضلك- بفضله!
What are you all doing?
ماذا تفعلون جميعا؟
You've angered the Immortal Huang Xian.
لقد أغضبت الخالد هوانغ شيان.
You're way too bold.
أنت جريء جدًا.
Don't be fooled by my thin looks.
لا تنخدع بمظهري النحيف.
I'm actually quite strong.
أنا قوية جدًا في الواقع.
Yes, yes.
نعم نعم.
Easy, easy.
سهل، سهل.
Easy.
سهل.
What if someone gets hurt?
ماذا لو أصيب أحد بأذى؟
Exactly.
بالضبط.
Great Immortal...
الخالد العظيم...
This young man is from out of town.
هذا الشاب من خارج المدينة.
He doesn't know our village's rules.
إنه لا يعرف قواعد قريتنا.
If he sincerely apologizes,
إذا اعتذر بصدق،
please forgive him this time.
أرجوك أن تسامحه هذه المرة.
No.
لا.
No matter what you hear soon,
بغض النظر عما تسمعه قريبا،
do not open your eyes.
لا تفتح عينيك.
Keep them shut and you'll stay alive.
أبقيهم مغلقين وسوف تبقى على قيد الحياة.
Where are you all going?
إلى أين أنتم ذاهبون جميعا؟
Groom!
زوج!
May you have a lifetime of harmony.
أتمنى لك حياة مليئة بالانسجام.
A fine marriage.
زواج جميل.
Congratulations.
مبروك.
Such joy!
كم هي فرحة!
Cheers!
هتافات!
A good thing.
شيء جيد.
Congratulations.
مبروك.
A talented groom and a lovely bride.
عريس موهوب وعروسة جميلة.
A match made in heaven.
مباراة صنعت في الجنة.
Cheers!
هتافات!
Groom!
زوج!
Why did you arrive so late?
لماذا وصلت متأخرا؟
The bride's been waiting anxiously.
العروس كانت تنتظر بفارغ الصبر.
How wonderful.
كم هو رائع.
Congratulations.
مبروك.
First bow: to heaven and earth.
القوس الأول : إلى السماء والأرض.
Second bow: to your elders.
الانحناءة الثانية: لكبار السن.
Third bow: to each other.
القوس الثالث : لبعضهم البعض .
The final salute.
التحية النهائية.
Drink the wedding wine.
اشرب نبيذ الزفاف.
May you never part till old age.
لا تفرق بينكما أبدا حتى الكبر.
I've had enough fun with you.
لقد استمتعت معك بما فيه الكفاية.
Righteous celestial power, light of the Seven Stars!
القوة السماوية الصالحة، نور النجوم السبعة!
All evil spirits, scatter with the wind!
كل الأرواح الشريرة، تبعثر مع الريح!
You have another trick?
هل لديك خدعة أخرى؟
Groom, do you think you can escape?
العريس هل تعتقد أنك تستطيع الهروب؟
I don't care if you're the Immortal Huang Xian or not.
لا يهمني إذا كنت هوانغ شيان الخالد أم لا.
Your time is up.
لقد انتهى وقتك.
Using incense as a cover,
استخدام البخور كغطاء،
your smoke trick can't fool me.
خدعة الدخان الخاصة بك لا يمكن أن تخدعني.
So it was you after all.
لقد كنت أنت بعد كل شيء.
You actually broke my illusion.
لقد كسرت وهمي فعلا.
You've got some real skill.
لديك بعض المهارات الحقيقية.
But this time, you'll fall to me.
ولكن هذه المرة سوف تقع في حبي.
It's just your bad luck.
إنه مجرد سوء حظك.
Do it!
افعلها!
You old bastard!
أيها الوغد العجوز!
You really want me dead, huh?
هل تريدني حقا أن أموت، أليس كذلك؟
No respect for law or heaven!
لا احترام للقانون أو الجنة!
Lawless!
خارج عن القانون!
Here, I am the law!
هنا أنا القانون!
Stop!
قف!
This is one of the House of Bai.
هذا هو أحد بيوت باي.
Let's see who dares touch him.
دعونا نرى من يجرؤ على لمسه.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
You don't recognize me?
أنت لا تعرفني؟
You really don't know me?
هل أنت حقا لا تعرفني؟
You don't even respect the House of Bai?
أنت لا تحترم حتى بيت باي؟
The House of Bai.
بيت باي.
Out here, the emperor is far away.
هنا، الإمبراطور بعيد.
I could kill you all and dump you in the ravine.
أستطيع أن أقتلكم جميعًا وألقي بكم في الوادي.
Who could stop me?
من يستطيع ايقافي؟
Do it!
افعلها!
You.
أنت.
Spirit gives birth to all, guided by the underworld.
الروح تلد الجميع، بقيادة العالم السفلي.
I cast a command, spirits roam everywhere.
ألقي أمرًا، والأرواح تتجول في كل مكان.
Reveal yourselves at once!
اكشفوا عن أنفسكم على الفور!
Defy me and enter the realm of oblivion.
تحداني وأدخل عالم النسيان.